这是普通高等学校招生
全国统一考试英语科听力部分。
该部分分为第一、第二两节。
注意：回答听力部分时，
请先。
先将答案标在试卷上。
听力部分结束前，你将有两分钟的时间
将你的答案转涂到答题卡上。
听力试音时间。
I read about your club in the paper today, and I thought I'd phone to find out a bit
more. Yes, certainly.
Well, we're a sort of social club for people from different countries.
It's quite a new club.
We have about 50 members at the moment, but we're growing all the time.
That sounds interesting.
I'm British, actually, and I came to Washington about three months ago.
I'm looking for ways to meet people.
What kinds of events do you Well, we have social get -togethers and sports events,
and we also have language evenings.
Could you tell me something about the language evenings?
Yes. Every day except Thursday, we have a language evening.
People can come and practice their languages, you know, over a drink or something.
We have different languages on different evenings.
Monday, Spanish, Tuesday, Italian, Wednesday, German, and Friday, French.
On Thursday, we usually have a meal in a restaurant for anyone who wants to come.
Well, that sounds great.
I really need to practice my French.
Okay. Well, if you can just give me your name and address, I'll send you the form
and some more information.
If you join now, you can have the first month free.
试音到此结束。
听力考试。
日，正式开始。
请看听力部分第一节。
第一节，听下面。
五段对话，每段对话后有一个小题。
从题中所给的
三个选项中，选出最佳选项，并标在试卷的相应位置。
听完每段。
看对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间
来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
每段对话仅读一遍。
例如，现在你有。
五秒钟的时间看试卷上的例题。
你将听到以下内容：
Excuse me, can you tell me how much the shirt is?
Yes, it's 9.15.
你将有五秒钟的时间，将正确答案
标在试卷上。
衬衫的价格为九磅十五便士，
所以你选择
项，并将其标在。试卷上。
现在，你有五秒钟的时间
阅读第一小题的有关内容。
What are we going to get for Lydia's birthday?
How about a pair of running shoes?
You know she hates doing exercise.
Then I guess we can buy her a birthday cake?
Excuse me, do you have time to help take a picture of us?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I've got to catch a bus.
That's It really annoys me when Kate calls her friends during office hours.
If I were you, I would tell her to stop.
Maybe you're right.
I will talk to her sometime.
Here's the menu, madame.
Would you like something to drink?
Yes, please. May I see the wine list?
Certainly. Here you are.
We need to have some fresh air.
Do you mind my opening the window?
As a matter of fact, I'm feeling a bit cold.
第一节到此结束。
第二节，听下面五段对话或独白。
每段对话或独白后有。
一个小题：从题中所给的
B, question lasts Answer
三个选项中，选出最佳选项，并标在试卷的相应位置。
听每段对话或独白前，
你将有时间。
阅读各个小题，每小题
五秒钟。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白读两遍
听下面一段对话，回答
第六和第七两个小题。
现在你有十秒钟的时间
阅读这两个小题。
I'll be doing some small repairs inside and outside the hotel.
I'll be cutting grass and taking care of the flowers.
Sounds interesting. What's the pay?
Well, about fifteen dollars an hour, five hours a day, and Sunday free.
That's good money.
What are you going to do with it?
I'll pay for the textbooks for next term.
Guess what I'll be doing this summer?
What? I'm going to work at the Riverside Hotel.
exactly will you be doing?
Let's see. I'll be doing some small repairs inside and outside the hotel.
I'll be cutting grass and taking care of the flowers.
Sounds interesting. What's the pay?
Well, about fifteen dollars an hour, five hours a day, and Sunday free.
That's good money.
What are you going to do with it?
I'll pay for the textbooks for next term.
听下面一段对话，回答
第八和第九两个小题。
现在。
你有十秒钟的时间阅读这两个小题。
Hi, Sue. How's it going?
Oh, hi, Frank.
Just fine. How are your classes?
Pretty good. I'm glad this is my last term here, though.
Why is that?
I thought you were enjoying school.
I was, but now I'm getting tired of it.
I'm ready for the real world.
What are you planning to do when you graduate?
First, I want to get a job as a computer programmer, and then after five years or
so, I'd like to start my own business.
Sounds good. I still have three terms to go until I'm done.
You'll make it for sure.
Well, see you later.
Bye. Hi, Sue.
How's it going?
Oh, hi, Frank.
Just fine. How are your classes?
Pretty good. I'm glad this is my last term here, though.
Why is that?
I thought you were enjoying school.
I was, but now I'm getting tired of it.
I'm ready for the real world.
What are you planning to do when you graduate?
First, I want to get a job as a computer programmer, and then after five years or
so, I'd like to start my own business.
Sounds good. I still have three terms to go until I'm done.
You'll make it for sure.
Well, see you later.
Bye. Hello, Milton Hotel Reservations.
听下面一段对话，回答
第十至第十二三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
How may I assist you?
Hi, I'm calling to make some changes to an existing reservation.
Certainly. Do you have the reservation number?
Sure. It's 219.
That's a reservation for Sally Menkel.
Is that right?
Yes, that's right.
I'd like to change the check -in date from September 15th to September 16th.
Certainly. I can make that change for you.
Is that the only change?
No. The check -out date will also change from the 23rd to the 24th.
No problem. We have you arriving on the 16th of September and leaving the 24th
September altogether eight nights.
Will there be anything else?
Yes. Instead of a courtyard room, I'd like a room with a view, preferably on an
upper floor. I can certainly change that for you, but there will be a change in the
room rate. The new rate is $199 per night, instead of original $179.
That's okay. These are all the changes.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome. Have a nice day.
Hello, Milton Hotel Reservations.
How may I assist you?
Hi. I'm calling to make some changes to an existing reservation.
Certainly. Do you have the reservation number?
Sure. It's 219.
That's a reservation for Sally Menkel.
Is that right?
Yes, that's right.
I'd like to change the check -in date from September 15th to September 16th.
Certainly. I can make that change for you.
Is that the only change?
No. The check -out date will also change from the 23rd to the 24th.
No problem. We have you arriving on the 16th of September and leaving the 24th
September altogether eight nights.
Will there be anything else?
Yes. Instead of a courtyard room, I'd like a room with a view, preferably on an
upper floor. I can certainly change that for you, but there will be a change in the
room rate. The new rate is $199 per night, instead of original $179.
That's okay. These are all the changes.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome. Have a nice day.
听下面一段对话，回答
第十三。
至第十六四个小题。
现在，你有二十秒钟的时间
阅读这四个小题。
Gordon, I'm going to Keswick in the Lake District this weekend.
Really? Yeah, five of us.
Why don't you join us?
We're getting to Keswick on Friday, then we're going boating on Saturday, and on
Sunday we're going to do some shopping.
Then I will take some time to visit my Aunt Lucy.
You're not going to camp, are you?
Isn't it a cold?
No, we're not.
It is a bit cold.
We're staying in a country inn.
It's not like five -star hotels or anything, but it's really comfortable.
sounds interesting. You know, it's the boating that I don't like.
Well, what are you up to?
Sit on my sofa all weekend and watch the DVDs I've just bought.
And that will be a busy weekend.
I may finish watching Friends.
I don't know how you can do that all weekend, Gordon.
I'd get bored.
I know, I know.
But that's really what I want to do.
Gordon, I'm going to Keswick in the Lake District this weekend.
Really? Yeah, five of us.
Why don't you join us?
We're getting to Keswick on Friday, then we're going boating on Saturday, and on
Sunday we're going to do some shopping.
Then I will take some time to visit my Aunt Lucy.
You're not going to camp, are you?
Isn't it a cold?
No, we're not.
It is a bit cold.
We're staying in a country inn.
It's not like five -star hotels or anything, but it's really comfortable.
sounds interesting. You know, it's the boating that I don't like.
Well, what are you up to?
Sit on my sofa all weekend and watch the DVDs I've just bought.
And that will be a busy weekend.
I may finish watching Friends.
I don't know how you can do that all weekend, Gordon.
I'd get bored.
I know, I know.
But that's really what I want to do.
听下面一段独白。
回答第十七至第二十四个小题。
现在你有二十秒钟的时间
阅读这四个小题。
Hello, welcome to the program.
In America, May and June are the traditional months for graduations.
A listener in China, Wang Ming, who is about to get an engineering degree, wants to
know how American college graduates find jobs.
Right now, the answer is, not very easily.
A latest study on the college job market showed that employers wanted to 22
fewer graduates this year than last.
The study also showed that just 20 of those who looked for jobs before graduation
have found one by now.
This is compared to half of students who had looked for a job by this time two years
ago. But one difference.
Fewer of this year's graduates have started to search for jobs.
Engineering graduates were more likely to have started their job search already, and
to have accepted a job.
This is among the best paid professions for people with just a college degree.
On average, engineering majors expect to start at about $62,000 a year.
Hello, welcome to the program.
In America, May and June are the traditional months for graduations.
A listener in China, Wang Ming, who is about to get an engineering degree, wants to
know how American college graduates find jobs.
Right now, the answer is, not very easily.
The answer is, Engineering graduates were more likely to have started their job
search already, and to have accepted a job.
This is among the best paid professions for people with just a college degree.
On average, engineering majors expect to start at about $62,000 a year.
第二节到此结束。
现在，你有两分钟的时间
将试卷上的答案转涂到答题卡上。
Thank you. Thank you.
听力部分到此结束。